<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Taylored Technology</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Taylored Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 09:52:40 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/legal/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 09:52:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>This Privacy Policy was last modified on April 04, 2014.
Taylored Technology Pty Ltd, ABN: 67 168 526 690 (&#34;us&#34;, &#34;we&#34;, or &#34;our&#34;) operates https://tayloredtechnology.net (the &#34;Site&#34;). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms Conditions</title>
      <link>/legal/terms-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 09:52:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/terms-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions (&#34;Agreement&#34;)
This Agreement was last modified on April 04, 2014.
Please read these Terms and Conditions (&#34;Agreement&#34;, &#34;Terms and Conditions&#34;) carefully before using https://tayloredtechnology.net (&#34;the Site&#34;) operated by Taylored Technology Pty Ltd, ABN: 67 168 526 690 (&#34;us&#34;, &#34;we&#34;, or &#34;our&#34;). This Agreement sets forth the legally binding terms and conditions for your use of the Site at https://tayloredtechnology.net.
By accessing or using the Site in any manner, including, but not limited to, visiting or browsing the Site or contributing content or other materials to the Site, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returns &amp; Refunds</title>
      <link>/legal/returns-refunds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 09:51:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/returns-refunds/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for shopping at Taylored Technology.
If you are not entirely satisfied with your purchase, we&#39;re here to help.
Returns
You have 30 days calendar days to return an item from the date you received it.
To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. Your item must be in the original packaging.
Your item needs to have the receipt or proof of purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Content License</title>
      <link>/legal/content-license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 13:27:22 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/legal/content-license/</guid>
      <description>Content is released under Mozilla Public License Version 2.0
 Definitions  1.1. &amp;ldquo;Contributor&amp;rdquo; means each individual or legal entity that creates, contributes to the creation of, or owns Covered Software.
1.2. &amp;ldquo;Contributor Version&amp;rdquo; means the combination of the Contributions of others (if any) used by a Contributor and that particular Contributor&amp;rsquo;s Contribution.
1.3. &amp;ldquo;Contribution&amp;rdquo; means Covered Software of a particular Contributor.
1.4. &amp;ldquo;Covered Software&amp;rdquo; means Source Code Form to which the initial Contributor has attached the notice in Exhibit A, the Executable Form of such Source Code Form, and Modifications of such Source Code Form, in each case including portions thereof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Operational Platform</title>
      <link>/engagements/internet-operational-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:21:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/internet-operational-platform/</guid>
      <description>Project Information For a business to be successful online, they need to split their time and effort across many specialized tools to not only drive traffic to their website but coordinate marketing, optimize conversion and ensure suitable uptime of services. We created an integrated operational platform that centralized all the critical success services for SME’s into one dashboard through a WordPress centric approach.
Business Transformation  Upwards of 50% time &amp;amp; effort reductions for SME’s to acquire and convert customers into sales Internet ‘overwhelm’ drastically reduced with integrated in-store POS, inventory &amp;amp; drop-shipping management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Micro Paas</title>
      <link>/engagements/wordpress-micro-paas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:19:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/wordpress-micro-paas/</guid>
      <description>Project Information WordPress hosting can be an incredibly painful ecosystem, core WordPress wouldn’t satisfy business needs, and some clients required over 160+ plugins to be installed to suit business needs with updates needing to be rolled out daily, and the potential of breaking changes being introduced with each update clients, vigorous backups, staging environments and roll-backs were essential.
Business Transformation Every WordPress hosting provide was evaluated, ranked and tested against our most complex clients with varying results ultimately highlighting the flaws of traditional hosting where larger servers were allocated to handle increased traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Warehouse</title>
      <link>/engagements/data-warehouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:18:29 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/data-warehouse/</guid>
      <description>Project Background This $16 Million project was tasked with creating a Big Data system to centralize fragmented customer data from multiple legacy and specialized systems such as claims, quotes, external brokers, &amp;amp; billing to name a few.
Business Transformation  Original state was a still running 1970 DB2 mainframe with pieces of data scattered across many customer systems. CGU had budgeted $16 Million to centralize all data into a new DB2 Infomatica database cluster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Level Dns</title>
      <link>/engagements/top-level-dns/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:17:35 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/top-level-dns/</guid>
      <description>Project Background AusRegistry Group was constructing infrastructure for expanding their management from the .au ccTLD to other DNS 2.0 ccTLD’s where the traditional .com .net’s were expanded into offerings such as .australia or .next
Business Transformation  Significant savings in licence fees, code compilation time &amp;amp; code quality were achieved through awareness and integration of powerful, proven open source tools that outperformed the existing commercially licensed alternatives. Systematic approach was implemented to transition the development team from the belief that CI tools such as Jenkins were blockers highlighting challenges in code quality to enables for rapid builds and deployment work-flows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Mobile Delivery</title>
      <link>/engagements/continuous-mobile-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:15:47 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/continuous-mobile-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Clients enabled  Australia: INGDirect, NAB, Vodafone Hutchinson, Coles, Telstra Asia Pacific: CIMB (Malaysia), NTT Docomo (Japan), NTT Data (Sapporo Japan), IBM (Japan), Acrodea (Japan) USA: DeutscheBank  Project Information Each of the clients had similar challenges in that they were actively developing and deploying mobile applications to multi platform phones. They had various security requirements such as Two Factor Verification, new user registration, root detection, phone number identity, and push notifications that all required the introduction of a ‘Stabilizing’ phase into their software development life-cycles slowing product delivery and increasing the risk of customer facing escaped defects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:07:43 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>What we do … A collective of Technologists, with a common shared passion and pursuit:
 Uniting the Heart of Humanity with the Gift of Technology
 … Its our mantra, our calling and foundation of all interactions with our clients. Technology was made to serve man, and we have enabled organizations of all sizes and industries to achieve a successful intertwining of their technology where time, money and operational costs are drastically cut, or opportunities for revenue surfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>/engagements/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:07:43 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Clients Enabled Trading Houses in the Foreign Exchange &amp;amp; Futures Markets
Project Information The art of trading a has resulted in a number of different systems, rules and approaches each with varying results. We were tasked to create a way of increasing profits of any existing trading system through a deep understanding of the underlying markets by optimizing entry and exit price for any trading decision made by a trading system or trader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/engagements/machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 10:07:43 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/engagements/machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Project Information Our client(s) wanted to expand the user personalization approach to websites to accelerate conversions and increase return on their marketing campaigns. There were already a world of tools available for interacting, understanding and optimizing conversion flows for known or logged in users, but its a green-field environment for anonymous users ‘if’ its possible to identify, track and categorize their interactions into a demographic &amp;amp; segment rapidly.
Business Transformation Prior to our involvement the primary method of interacting with ‘anonymous’ users was to subscribe to a large multi-geographical service (such as Facebook or Google) that the ‘anonymous’ user would already be logged into that’s prepared to share non PII (Personally Identifiable Information) with the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/</guid>
      <description>If time; money; operational costs; or efficiency are some of your major concerns then we can help be your technology enabler. We’ve helped companies of all sizes from micro business through to major international enterprise with their Technology challenges. Everything we do follows basal NextGen principles.
Our ‘A la Carte’ menu of NexGen services is as follows:
Web &amp;amp; Social Optimization … Built on over 15 years of SEO (Search Engine Optimization) experience we strip away the complexities of understanding the technical aspects through detailed reports &amp;amp; technical step by step recommendations to fix issues enabling business to hold their current SEO company accountable for their work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taylored Technology</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Us   (function() { var qs,js,q,s,d=document, gi=d.getElementById, ce=d.createElement, gt=d.getElementsByTagName, id=&#34;typef_orm&#34;, b=&#34;https://embed.typeform.com/&#34;; if(!gi.call(d,id)) { js=ce.call(d,&#34;script&#34;); js.id=id; js.src=b+&#34;embed.js&#34;; q=gt.call(d,&#34;script&#34;)[0]; q.parentNode.insertBefore(js,q) } })()  powered by Typeform         Send Message   --  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>